Guide to the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection, 1985-2005 RL.01138
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sarah Dyer Zine collection
1985-2005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Dyer, Sarah
RL.01138
18.3 Linear Feet
2050 Items
Approximately 2000 individual zines and nearly 800 titles, most self-published by women and girls 1985-2000. Most were produced in the United States, a few come from Canada and other countries. In-house database with subject access available. Subjects include feminism, riot grrrl, body image and consciousness, sexual abuse, music, mental illness, film, poetry, rock and punk music, comics, violence against women, sexual identity, homosexuality and bisexuality, and erotica. The collection includes four audiocassette tapes and one VHS tape. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Sarah Dyer Zine Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2000, and additions were received in 2002, 2006, and 2008.
Biographical Note
Sarah Dyer is the creator of Action Girl Comics, an anthology that she started in 1994 to spotlight the work of women who were self-publishing comics of their own. Prior to starting Action Girl Comics, Dyer was the publisher of Action Girl News, which reviewed women's and girls' zines. This collection consists of the zines submitted to her for review.
Collection Overview
Approximately 2000 individual zines and nearly 800 titles, most self-published by women and girls 1985-2000. Most were produced in the United States, a few come from Canada and other countries. In-house database with subject access available. Subjects include feminism, riot grrrl, body image and consciousness, sexual abuse, music, mental illness, film, poetry, rock and punk music, comics, violence against women, sexual identity, homosexuality and bisexuality, and erotica. The collection includes four audiocassette tapes and one VHS tape. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Addition #1 (2002-0319) contains approximately 150 titles.
Addition #2 (2006-0068) contains approximately 150 titles and are separated into two groups: those authored by women and those authored by men.
Addition #3 (2008-0030) contains approximately 175 titles and one VHS tape.
Related Material
Researchers should consult the Bingham Center Zine Collection database, which includes additional resources about zines as well as an essay by Sarah Dyer entitled My Life in Zines.
Feminism -- United States; Underground press publications -- United States; Mental illness; Self-publishing; Young women -- United States -- Social life and customs; Fan magazines; Periodicals -- Publishing -- United States; Women's periodicals, American; American poetry -- 20th century; Women poets; Abused women; Women -- Psychology; Heterosexuality; Sexual orientation; Lesbianism; Homosexuality; Comic books, strips, etc.; Women -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Erotica; Dyer, Sarah; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
- Sarah Dyer Zine Collection, 1985-2005, 7 boxes
  - box 1 (Box 1)
    - 13 (Box 1)
    - 20 Bus (Box 1)
    - 100% (Box 1)
    - 105% Real (Box 1)
    - Ablaze (Box 1)
    - Absolute Beginners (Box 1)
    - Action Girl Guide (Box 1)
    - Action Girl Newsletter (Box 1)
    - Aim (Box 1)
    - Aim Your Dick (Box 1)
    - Alice the Camel (Box 1)
    - Alien (Box 1)
    - Alien Girl (Box 1)
    - Aliencola (Box 1)
    - All Hail Me (Box 1)
    - Amelia Jane (Box 1)
    - Ancilla (Box 1)
    - Angel Cake (Box 1)
    - Angelfish (Box 1)
    - Angst and Depression (Box 1)
    - Animal Snap (Box 1)
    - Anna Bee (Box 1)
    - annoying girl (Box 1)
    - Anti-Hero Presents... (Box 1)
    - Applegate Skinner (Box 1)
    - Aqua Girl Star (Box 1)
    - Astro Delight (Box 1)
    - Attack! (Box 1)
    - Baby Nebula (Box 1)
    - Babydoll (Box 1)
    - Back in the Drivers Seat (Box 1)
    - Backchat (Box 1)
    - Bad Girls (Box 1)
    - Ball-Buster (Box 1)
    - Ballroom (Box 1)
    - Bamboo Girl (Box 1)
    - The Banshee (Box 1)
    - Barbie Can Kick G.I. Joe's Ass (Box 1)
    - Bathory's Blister (Box 1)
    - Bathroom Hill (Box 1)
    - Beautiful Bras and Bodyhair (Box 1)
    - Bedtime Stories for Trivial Teens (Box 1)
    - Beri-Beri (Box 1)
    - Besmirched (Box 1)
    - Better Than Barbie (Box 1)
    - Betty Stained (Box 1)
    - Bi-Girl World (Box 1)
    - Billy's Mitten (Box 1)
    - Birthday Girl (Box 1)
    - Bitch (Box 1)
    - The Bitch Manifesto (Box 1)
    - Bitchcraft Inc. (Box 1)
    - Bleu Cheese On Fire (Box 1)
    - Blinkmoxy (Box 1)
    - Blister (Box 1)
    - Blistering Holiday (Box 1)
    - Blowin Chunxxx (Box 1)
    - Blue Ballad (Box 1)
    - Blue Candy (Box 1)
    - Blue Stocking (Box 1)
    - Boji (Box 1)
    - Bomb (Box 1)
    - The Bone (Box 1)
    - Bonnie the Stalker (Box 1)
    - Booby Trap (Box 1)
    - Boredom Sucks (Box 1)
    - Boy Food (Box 1)
    - Boy/Girl (Box 1)
    - Brains (Box 1)
    - Brassy Girl Newsletter (Box 1)
    - Briar Rose (Box 1)
    - Broom (Box 1)
    - Buckeye Zines (Box 1)
    - Bulldozer (Box 1)
    - Bullshit (Box 1)
    - Bus 6 (Box 1)
    - Busboy (Box 1)
    - Bust (Box 1)
    - Busy Bea's Bush (Box 1)
    - C.I.A. (Box 1)
    - Calico (Box 1)
    - Candles for Girls (Box 1)
    - Cantinho das Felinas (Box 1)
    - Caption (Box 1)
    - Catch of the Day (Box 1)
    - Catherine's Hair (Box 1)
    - Catscratch (Box 1)
    - Cathy's Unconventional No-Nonsense Tour de Force (Box 1)
    - CaveGirl (Box 1)
    - Certain Comfort (Box 1)
    - Certifiable (Box 1)
    - Charm School (Box 1)
    - Cheshire (Box 1)
    - Chica Loca (Box 1)
    - Chocolate Impulse (Box 1)
    - Chronic and Recurrant Upper Respitory Infection (Box 1)
    - C'est La Vie (Box 1)
    - Cheese Log (Box 1)
    - Cherry Bomb (Box 1)
    - Chickfactor (Box 1)
    - Clinch Zine (Box 1)
    - Clitoris (Box 1)
    - Clownhead (Box 1)
    - C'mon Swing It (Box 1)
    - Coagulated Comics Coallide (Box 1)
    - Coddle (Box 1)
    - Confessions of a Weird, Weird, Weird Kid (Box 1)
    - Conscious Clit (Box 1)
    - Cooking on the Edge (Box 1)
    - Corpse/Respondents (Box 1)
    - Cosmic Pixie Grit (Box 1)
    - The Crazy Daisy (Box 1)
    - Crème Brulèe (Box 1)
    - a crooked stave (Box 1)
    - Crummies in Tummies (Box 1)
    - Crumpy (Box 1)
  - box 2 (Box 2)
    - Crystal Blue Persuasion (Box 2)
    - Cul-de-Sac (Box 2)
    - Cupsize (Box 2)
    - Cusp (Box 2)
    - Cutiepie (Box 2)
    - D.I.W. (Box 2)
    - Daffodil (Box 2)
    - The Daily The (Box 2)
    - Danger Prone Daphne (Box 2)
    - Dan's Morning Schedule (Box 2)
    - The Daughters of Houdini (Box 2)
    - Davotchka (Box 2)
    - A Day in the Life Of... (Box 2)
    - Dead Jackie Susann Quarterly (Box 2)
    - Definition of GRRRL and Other Rants (Box 2)
    - Dementia Praecox (Box 2)
    - Den Den (Box 2)
    - Design Number 816 (Box 2)
    - Die Right Now (Box 2)
    - Dig (Box 2)
    - Disarm (Box 2)
    - Disco Fred's Got a Vasectomy (Box 2)
    - Dish (Box 2)
    - The Dissonant Accost (Box 2)
    - Distill the Life (Box 2)
    - Diversity (Box 2)
    - Doll (Box 2)
    - Donation (Box 2)
    - Don't Be a Pussy (Box 2)
    - Don't Even... (Box 2)
    - Dork Dyke (Box 2)
    - Downer (Box 2)
    - Dracula Meets Jesus (Box 2)
    - drip (Box 2)
    - Drum Core (Box 2)
    - Drunken Reflexions (Box 2)
    - Ea (Box 2)
    - eggplant (Box 2)
    - Electro-Girl (Box 2)
    - Elsker (Box 2)
    - Elysium Lie (Box 2)
    - Emotion (Box 2)
    - The Endemic Other (Box 2)
    - Endemoniada (Box 2)
    - The Epic Chronicles of Bromeyer (Box 2)
    - Epiphyte (Box 2)
    - Euphoria (Box 2)
    - Every Girl's Dream (Box 2)
    - Everything I Touch Turns To Shit and Garbage (Box 2)
    - ew, that's gross! (Box 2)
    - Exhibit A (Box 2)
    - Exile (Box 2)
    - Exurbia (Box 2)
    - Eye of the Kudzu (Box 2)
    - Fake (Box 2)
    - The Family Next Door (Box 2)
    - Fanny (Box 2)
    - Fantastic Fanzine (Box 2)
    - Fat Cheeks (Box 2)
    - Fat Ugly Venus (Box 2)
    - Feeding the Fowls (Box 2)
    - Fem Power (Box 2)
    - Femcore (Box 2)
    - Feminist Collections (Box 2)
    - Femme Flicke (Box 2)
    - First Person (Box 2)
    - Flashpoint (Box 2)
    - Flatter! (Box 2)
    - Flush (Box 2)
    - The Flying Apparatus (Box 2)
    - The Flying Bitch Sisters Present... (Box 2)
    - The Fly Paper (Box 2)
    - Freak (Box 2)
    - Free Gurlz (Box 2)
    - Free Lost Girl (Box 2)
    - Freek of Nayture (Box 2)
    - From Far Off (Box 2)
    - From the Gut (Box 2)
    - Fuckchop (Box 2)
    - Fuel (Box 2)
    - Function (Box 2)
    - Garbles (Box 2)
    - Gecko (Box 2)
    - Geckotopia (Box 2)
    - Geek Girl (Box 2)
    - Gelatinous Agar (Box 2)
    - Genius Gone Insane (Box 2)
    - GERLL Zine Distro (Box 2)
    - Get Off My Property (Box 2)
    - Getting Out of Bed (Box 2)
    - Ginger's Hut (Box 2)
    - Gingersnap (Box 2)
    - Girl Band Guide (Box 2)
    - Girl Cola (Box 2)
    - Girl Czar (Box 2)
    - Girl Germs (Box 2)
    - Girl Girl (Box 2)
    - Girl Luv (Box 2)
    - Girl Scene City (Box 2)
    - Girl Zine Show (Box 2)
    - Girlfiend (Box 2)
    - Girljock (Box 2)
    - Girlilla Art Girls Zine (Box 2)
    - Gizmo (Box 2)
    - Glitter (Box 2)
    - Global Mail (Box 2)
    - Gobnascale (Box 2)
    - Goddess Juice (Box 2)
  - box 3 (Box 3)
    - Gogglebox (Box 3)
    - Good Auspice Wish (Box 3)
    - Gorf (Box 3)
    - Graham Cracker Cereal (Box 3)
    - Gravee (Box 3)
    - Great Day for Up (Box 3)
    - Green Fire (Box 3)
    - Grope (Box 3)
    - Grot Grrrl (Box 3)
    - GRRL (Box 3)
    - Grrl-a-Liscious (Box 3)
    - Gumption (Box 3)
    - Gumshoe (Box 3)
    - Gunmoll (Box 3)
    - Gurken (Box 3)
    - Gurlz With Gunz (Box 3)
    - H2S04 (Box 3)
    - Habitual Freak (Box 3)
    - Hag (Box 3)
    - Hag Rag (Box 3)
    - Hallucinatory Amnesia (Box 3)
    - Harsh (Box 3)
    - Hazmat (Box 3)
    - Hearts Can Starve (Box 3)
    - Heartworms (Box 3)
    - Hell Kitty (Box 3)
    - Hellion (Box 3)
    - Her Own Bad Self (Box 3)
    - Herd (Box 3)
    - Heresies (Box 3)
    - Heroine (Box 3)
    - Hey Gurly (Box 3)
    - Hey! I Want To Be In Your Zine (Box 3)
    - Hey There, Barbie Girl! (Box 3)
    - Hip Mama (Box 3)
    - Hissy Fitt (Box 3)
    - Hit It or Quit It (Box 3)
    - Hodge Podge (Box 3)
    - Honey and Ribbons (Box 3)
    - Honeysuckle (Box 3)
    - Hope (Box 3)
    - Hot Lunch (Box 3)
    - Hot Wire (Box 3)
    - Housewife Turned Assasin (Box 3)
    - How I Learned To Do It Bloody Murder (Box 3)
    - Huge Dead Animal (Box 3)
    - Hungry Girl Fanzine (Box 3)
    - Hurricane Girl (Box 3)
    - Hyperventilate (Box 3)
    - Hysteria (Box 3)
    - IBLOT Under the Milk (Box 3)
    - I Am the ThumbTack (Box 3)
    - The I Hate Brenda Newsletter (Box 3)
    - I Hate Valentine's Day (Box 3)
    - I Hate You (Box 3)
    - I Kicked A Boy (Box 3)
    - I Rule (Box 3)
    - I'm a Dimpled Lunatic (Box 3)
    - I'm Not a Feminist But... (Box 3)
    - Imaginary Grace (Box 3)
    - Impress Your Friends (Box 3)
    - In Your Face (Box 3)
    - Inferno (Box 3)
    - Invasion of the Killer Slut Monkey from Hell (Box 3)
    - Itchin for Ink (Box 3)
    - It's All a Gimmick of Some Sort (Box 3)
    - J.H. Knob (Box 3)
    - Jane Gets a Divorce (Box 3)
    - Jacaré (Box 3)
    - Jacknife (Box 3)
    - The Jelly Slide (Box 3)
    - The Jelly Bean (Box 3)
    - Jing Bang So (Box 3)
    - Joy and Spider (Box 3)
    - Jumbo Shrimp (Box 3)
    - Just Call Me K (Box 3)
    - Just Fine (Box 3)
    - Just Like a Girl (Box 3)
    - K.C. (Box 3)
    - Kablooie (Box 3)
    - Kelp (Box 3)
    - Ketchup (Box 3)
    - Kick It Over (Box 3)
    - Killers (Box 3)
    - King Size Queen (Box 3)
    - Kingfish (Box 3)
    - Kiss the Cook (Box 3)
    - Kitten (Box 3)
    - Kitten Core (Box 3)
    - Kitten Militant (Box 3)
    - Kitty Krap (Box 3)
    - Knee Deep in Oatmeal (Box 3)
    - Krazy (Box 3)
    - Kultprincess Suicide (Box 3)
    - The Ladies Art Revival (Box 3)
    - Ladybird (Box 3)
    - Lardass (Box 3)
    - The Last Seeds of the Night (Box 3)
    - The Latest News (Box 3)
    - A Lefty Makes a Better Cake (Box 3)
    - Lesbian Contradiction (Box 3)
  - box 4 (Box 4)
    - Let's Play Grrrl (Box 4)
    - Let's Start a Fucking Riot Girls (Box 4)
    - Liar (Box 4)
    - Libel (Box 4)
    - Life During Wartime (Box 4)
    - A Lighter Shade of Perixide (Box 4)
    - Lime Green News (Box 4)
    - Linch Pin (Box 4)
    - Limonophobio (Box 4)
    - Lisa Lionheart (Box 4)
    - Literal Bitch (Box 4)
    - Little Chick With a Gun In Her Hand (Box 4)
    - Little Girl (Box 4)
    - Live Beat (Box 4)
    - Living Hell Lady (Box 4)
    - Lizard Music (Box 4)
    - Loa (Box 4)
    - Lord Lindith's Handkerchief (Box 4)
    - Lost I.D. (Box 4)
    - Lost in the Land of Lobotomy (Box 4)
    - Loud As Hell (Box 4)
    - Lovelies Bleeding (Box 4)
    - Love Trinkets (Box 4)
    - Lumpy Head (Box 4)
    - Luna (Box 4)
    - Lunatic Fringe (Box 4)
    - Lunette (Box 4)
    - Lux (Box 4)
    - Lysistrata (Box 4)
    - MT Mailbox (Box 4)
    - Mad As Hell (Box 4)
    - Mad Planet (Box 4)
    - Madeline (Box 4)
    - MadWoman (Box 4)
    - Magic Trick (Box 4)
    - Make-Out Session (Box 4)
    - Mamasita (Box 4)
    - Man Candy (Box 4)
    - Manic Panic (Box 4)
    - Manifesto (Box 4)
    - Marmalade (Box 4)
    - Martyrman (Box 4)
    - Matter (Box 4)
    - Maybe (She Said) (Box 4)
    - Me and My Big Mouth (Box 4)
    - Me First, two folders (Box 4)
    - The Meat Hook (Box 4)
    - Media Darling (Box 4)
    - Meeting the Shadow (Box 4)
    - Mellow Daze (Box 4)
    - Melvin and Earl (Box 4)
    - Meniscus (Box 4)
    - Mesopotamia (Box 4)
    - Miau! (Box 4)
    - Microcosm (Box 4)
    - Midwest Girl Fest (Box 4)
    - Minor Heroine (Box 4)
    - Mohawk Beaver (Box 4)
    - Moist (Box 4)
    - Molasses Soulkiss (Box 4)
    - Mold (Box 4)
    - Mons of Venus (Box 4)
    - Moonfork (Box 4)
    - Mousie (Box 4)
    - Moxie (Box 4)
    - Mr. Bun (Box 4)
    - Mrs. Thomason's Dishes (Box 4)
    - Ms .45 (Box 4)
    - Ms. America (Box 4)
    - Muffin Bones (Box 4)
    - Murmurs (Box 4)
    - My Broken Halo (Box 4)
    - My Car Pinto (Box 4)
    - My Dear Delerious (Box 4)
    - My Last Nerve (Box 4)
    - My Little Box (Box 4)
    - My Tiara (Box 4)
    - Mystery Date (Box 4)
    - navy blue (Box 4)
    - Nerd Girl (Box 4)
    - nEuROTIC Girl (Box 4)
    - The New Girl Times (Box 4)
    - The News Down There (Box 4)
    - Nimble Fingers (Box 4)
    - No! (Box 4)
    - No Crud In It Gurlies (Box 4)
    - No Police State (Box 4)
    - No Puffin Please (Box 4)
    - Noisemakers (Box 4)
    - Noisy Jewelry (Box 4)
    - North Bi Northwest (Box 4)
    - Not Even (Box 4)
    - Not Your Bitch! (Box 4)
    - Notes In Response To a Dysfunctional Society (Box 4)
    - Nutmeg (Box 4)
    - Obsessions (Box 4)
    - Ocho y Media (Box 4)
    - Odds 'n Ends (Box 4)
    - Off My Jammy (Box 4)
    - Off Our Backs (Box 4)
    - Oh... (Box 4)
    - Oh, Bite Me. It's Fun! (Box 4)
    - Oh Oh Cheri (Box 4)
    - Olive's Oyl (Box 4)
    - On The Ray (Box 4)
    - Ooompa! Oompa! (Box 4)
    - Oppression (Box 4)
    - Ordure (Box 4)
    - Original Cool (Box 4)
    - The Other 88% (Box 4)
    - Our Rag (Box 4)
    - Out of the Vortex (Box 4)
    - Outwardly Pleasant (Box 4)
    - Oya (Box 4)
    - The PandE Newsletter (Box 4)
    - Pam's Zine (Box 4)
    - Pandora (Box 4)
    - Pandora's Box (Box 4)
    - Panik (Box 4)
    - Panophobia (Box 4)
    - Paper Cuts (Box 4)
    - Paper Dolls (Box 4)
    - Paralyzed (Box 4)
  - box 5 (Box 5)
    - Parodia (Box 5)
    - Pasty (Box 5)
    - Patchwork Heart (Box 5)
    - Patti Smith (Box 5)
    - Pawholes (Box 5)
    - Peach (Box 5)
    - Pear Droppings (Box 5)
    - Pee (Box 5)
    - Peel (Box 5)
    - Peinyce Invee (Box 5)
    - Penis Envy (Box 5)
    - Pennies From Heaven (Box 5)
    - Penny's Fanzine (Box 5)
    - Pesky Meddling Girls (Box 5)
    - Picklejar (Box 5)
    - Pink[Hudson, NY] (Box 5)
    - Pink [North Hollywood, CA] (Box 5)
    - Pink Haired Jenny (Box 5)
    - Pink Kitty (Box 5)
    - Pink Peanuts (Box 5)
    - Pinkus Blank (Box 5)
    - Pippilotta In the Jampot (Box 5)
    - Pixie Girl (Box 5)
    - Placebo (Box 5)
    - Plaintive Wombat Gazette (Box 5)
    - Playn (Box 5)
    - Plexiform (Box 5)
    - Plotz (Box 5)
    - Plume (Box 5)
    - Plunger (Box 5)
    - Pocket (Box 5)
    - Poke (Box 5)
    - Pondering Hedgehog (Box 5)
    - Popcore (Box 5)
    - Popka (Box 5)
    - Pork and Beans (Box 5)
    - Poser (Box 5)
    - The Postmodern Adventures of JoJo Dyke (Box 5)
    - Pout (Box 5)
    - Power Candy (Box 5)
    - Presently Out of Product (Box 5)
    - Pretty Shield (Box 5)
    - Princess, two folders (Box 5)
    - Princess Charming (Box 5)
    - Provo-cat-ive (Box 5)
    - Pucker Up (Box 5)
    - Pups Zine (Box 5)
    - Pure Vamp (Box 5)
    - The Purple Marker (Box 5)
    - Purrve (Box 5)
    - Pussycat (Box 5)
    - Pussy Cat Vision (Box 5)
    - Queer (Box 5)
    - Racecar (Box 5)
    - Radbag (Box 5)
    - La Radiator (Box 5)
    - Rachel Zine (Box 5)
    - Rag (Box 5)
    - Rage Doll (Box 5)
    - Rage for Choice (Box 5)
    - Rain (Box 5)
    - Ramble and Ramble (Box 5)
    - Rampage (Box 5)
    - Rat the First (Box 5)
    - Rebel Girl (Box 5)
    - Residential Garbage (Box 5)
    - Resister (Box 5)
    - Revenge Of the Pink Surf Lizzard (Box 5)
    - Revolution 2000 AD (Box 5)
    - Rhode Islanduh (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl [Washington, DC] (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrl [New York, NY] (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Eureka/Arcata (Box 5)
    - Leeds and Bradford Riot Grrrl! (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Newsletter (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Press (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Review (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Vancouver (Box 5)
    - Riot Grrrl Victoria (Box 5)
    - Riotemptresses (Box 5)
    - Rise Above (Box 5)
    - Ritalin (Box 5)
    - rockcandy (Box 5)
    - Rocksteady Columbia Newsletter (Box 5)
    - Rollerderby (Box 5)
    - The Rose (Box 5)
    - Roso Dork (Box 5)
    - Rubberband (Box 5)
    - The Ruby Slippers (Box 5)
    - Ruckus (Box 5)
  - box 6 (Box 6)
    - The Rude Girl Press (Box 6)
    - Runt (Box 6)
    - Sacred River (Box 6)
    - Sad (Box 6)
    - Samsara (Box 6)
    - Sanimag (Box 6)
    - Sassiest Girl in America (Box 6)
    - Satan Wears a Bra (Box 6)
    - Sawtooth (Box 6)
    - Scarlet 'A' (Box 6)
    - Scented Verse (Box 6)
    - Schpargle (Box 6)
    - Scour (Box 6)
    - Scraps (Box 6)
    - Scratch (Box 6)
    - Scratch and Sniff (Box 6)
    - Scrawl (Box 6)
    - The Screaming Siren (Box 6)
    - Screams from Inside (Box 6)
    - Scruffy (Box 6)
    - The SCUM Manifesto (Box 6)
    - Second Skin (Box 6)
    - Secret (Box 6)
    - Secret Handshake (Box 6)
    - Secret Weapon (Box 6)
    - Self Esteem Queen (Box 6)
    - Sentimental Suitcase Stickers (Box 6)
    - Septophilia Records (Box 6)
    - Sewer (Box 6)
    - Sex with Bobby Briggs (Box 6)
    - Sexpot (Box 6)
    - Shadow Boxing (Box 6)
    - Shag Stamp (Box 6)
    - Shakeface (Box 6)
    - She Dresses the Lady Pioneers of the New Frontier (Box 6)
    - She God (Box 6)
    - Shelf Life (Box 6)
    - Shocking Pink (Box 6)
    - Shoujo Shuusan (Box 6)
    - Sino-Pup (Box 6)
    - Sisyphean Garbage (Box 6)
    - Sittin' Pretty (Box 6)
    - Shank (Box 6)
    - Skew (Box 6)
    - Skin Swing Feel (Box 6)
    - Slam Book (Box 6)
    - Slippery When Wet (Box 6)
    - Slowbrow Magazine (Box 6)
    - The Sludge Pond (Box 6)
    - Slug and Lettuce (Box 6)
    - Slumber (Box 6)
    - Slut Magnet (Box 6)
    - Slut Utopia (Box 6)
    - The Small Time Smirker (Box 6)
    - Smart Like Eve (Box 6)
    - Snakes, Snails, and Puppy Dog Tails (Box 6)
    - Snarla (Box 6)
    - Sneer (Box 6)
    - Soda Jerk (Box 6)
    - Sock Monkey (Box 6)
    - Solamente (Box 6)
    - Something Else (Box 6)
    - Sonic Girlfrienz (Box 6)
    - Sourpuss (Box 6)
    - Southern Hysteria (Box 6)
    - Sowkins (Box 6)
    - Space Craft Convention (Box 6)
    - Sparkly Kitty Stickers (Box 6)
    - Speak Out Magazine (Box 6)
    - Speedwell (Box 6)
    - Split (Box 6)
    - The Spiralling Vortex (Box 6)
    - Spit (Box 6)
    - Square One (Box 6)
    - Stain (Box 6)
    - Standard Deviation (Box 6)
    - Starache (Box 6)
    - Star Dust Memorys (Box 6)
    - Stifled (Box 6)
    - Stinkbomb (Box 6)
    - Stinkzine (Box 6)
    - Strawberry Shortcake (Box 6)
    - Structure (Box 6)
    - Stuffed Up (Box 6)
    - Stumble (Box 6)
    - Suburbia (Box 6)
    - Succubi (Box 6)
    - Suck My Dick (Box 6)
    - Sucky (Box 6)
    - El Sueño de Venus (Box 6)
    - Sugar and Spice (Box 6)
    - Sugarplum Fairy (Box 6)
    - Sunshine State Skanker (Box 6)
    - Superfly Fanzine (Box 6)
    - Super Girl (Box 6)
    - Super Heroine (Box 6)
    - Superfluous (Box 6)
    - Superkeen (Box 6)
    - Supine (Box 6)
    - Surfer Girl (Box 6)
    - Sweet Heart (Box 6)
    - Sweet Tooth (Box 6)
    - Switch Hitter (Box 6)
    - TWB (Box 6)
    - TVI (Box 6)
    - Take Back Your Life (Box 6)
    - Tales Calculated to Drive You to Albuquerque (Box 6)
  - box 7 (Box 7)
    - Tally (Box 7)
    - Tater Taught (Box 7)
    - Tattle Tale (Box 7)
    - Tease (Box 7)
    - Teenage Suicide (Box 7)
    - Tender Age in Bloom (Box 7)
    - Terror Zine (Box 7)
    - That Grrrl (Box 7)
    - Therapy (Box 7)
    - There's a Boy In the Girls' Bathroom (Box 7)
    - This Can Kill You (Box 7)
    - This Girl is Different (Box 7)
    - This Zine Is Called (Box 7)
    - Thorn (Box 7)
    - Three In One (Box 7)
    - Thrift Score (Box 7)
    - Thumper (Box 7)
    - Thunder Pussy (Box 7)
    - Tiger Lilie Girl (Box 7)
    - Tightrope (Box 7)
    - Transcendence (Box 7)
    - Tilo (Box 7)
    - Top? (Box 7)
    - Totally Fucked (Box 7)
    - Totally Hair Barbie (Box 7)
    - toy box (Box 7)
    - Trinity (Box 7)
    - Trouble Kid (Box 7)
    - Trout Parade (Box 7)
    - Two Cents (Box 7)
    - U.G.L.Y. (Box 7)
    - U Know Us Kids (Box 7)
    - The Umbrella Stand (Box 7)
    - The Unmentionable (Box 7)
    - Upslut (Box 7)
    - The Urban Herbalist (Box 7)
    - Valley Riot Grrrl (Box 7)
    - Vamp (Box 7)
    - Velocity Zine (Box 7)
    - Velvet Grass (Box 7)
    - Victoria's Secretions (Box 7)
    - Verboslammed (Box 7)
    - Violet (Box 7)
    - Violets Aren't Bad (Box 7)
    - Virus (Box 7)
    - Viscious Circles (Box 7)
    - Void (Box 7)
    - Vulvateen (Box 7)
    - W.A.A.M. (Box 7)
    - W.I.C.C.A. (Box 7)
    - A Wandering Eye (Box 7)
    - Watley-Browne Review (Box 7)
    - The Way the Beast Reproduces (Box 7)
    - Wayward Souls (Box 7)
    - We Like Poo (Box 7)
    - Wednesday (Box 7)
    - Wee Hours (Box 7)
    - Welcome To Our World (Box 7)
    - Wendy Darling (Box 7)
    - Whatever (Box 7)
    - When She Was Good (Box 7)
    - Wick (Box 7)
    - Wiglet (Box 7)
    - Wild Honey Pie (Box 7)
    - Wild Rumpus (Box 7)
    - Wild Womyn (Box 7)
    - William Wants a Doll (Box 7)
    - Wind-up Toaster Pastry (Box 7)
    - Winky Pinky (Box 7)
    - With Pleasure (Box 7)
    - Withering Snout (Box 7)
    - Wives Tales (Box 7)
    - The Woman Rebel (Box 7)
    - Womanzine (Box 7)
    - Wombat's World (Box 7)
    - The Women's Center (Box 7)
    - Women's Options (Box 7)
    - Women's Underground Music Directory (Box 7)
    - Wondergirrl's underpants (Box 7)
    - Worry Doll (Box 7)
    - Wrecking Ball (Box 7)
    - XX Sound (Box 7)
    - Y Is For Yuck (Box 7)
    - Yard Wide Yarns (Box 7)
    - Yawp (Box 7)